おう バイト
Hey, farmhand!
Hurry up and wake—
早く起きて…おっ？
八軒君
Hachiken-kun, isn't it tough
to wake up at 5 AM every day?
毎日５時起きでしんどくないかい？
大丈夫です
No, it's fine!
I always wake up at 4 AM
for the equestrian club!
馬術部がいつも４時起きなので
じゃ あしたから４時起きにすっか
Then let's start your day at
4 AM beginning tomorrow!
Oh, please no.
勘弁してくださいよー
Damn you, farmhand!
己 バイト
それしきの働きっぷりで俺が認めると思うなよ
Don't think I'll accept you
just because you work hard.
父さん 邪魔
Dad, you're in the way.
おう バイト これ 運んどけ
Hey, farmhand!
Carry these!
はいっ
Okay!
これ 直しとけ
Fix this!
はいっ
Okay!
これ 片付けとけ
Put these away!
はいっ
Okay!
Damn you, farmhand!
己 バイト
父さん 邪魔
Dad, you're in the way.
本格的な夏の日差しが
肌を焦がしていく様に
私もあなたに恋焦がれる
海へドライブ 運転するよ
横顔撫でる 潮風が気持ちいいsummer day
la la la summer day
ビーチパラソルカラフルだ yeah
砂浜に咲く　花みたい
KISS YOU あなたの心
もっともっと近くにいたい　感じたい
私だけ見て
KISS YOU ぐっと膨らんだ
胸の思い　唇にのせて　伝えたいと
だから　KISS YOU
だから　さあ　KISS YOU
Episode 08
Hachiken
Makes a Huge Mistake
ちょっと休憩するべ
Let's take a break.
Sure.
そうね
八軒君もお茶にしましょ
Hachiken-kun, why don't you
join us for some tea?
八軒君？
Hachiken-kun?!
Yes?!
あっ はい
Oh...
Are you okay?
大丈夫かい
あぁ はい
Um, yes!
無理しないで休みな
Don't push yourself too much.
Take a break.
疲れを取るのも仕事のうちだよ
Taking care of yourself
is part of work.
父ちゃんも病み上がりなんだからね
Pa, you're still recovering, too!
I'm okay.
俺 大丈夫ですから
But being a live-in farmhand is tough,
そうは言ってもね
泊まり込みでバイトなんてしんどくて当たり前なんだから
no matter what you say.
Still, I'll try my best!
いえ 頑張ります
I mean, please let me try.
つーか 頑張らせてください
Well, it's just that
いや… 俺 実は将来やりたいことがなくてですね
I don't really have a sense
of what I want to do with my future.
その…進路で悩んでる友達の相談に乗りたくても
And, um,
even though I want to support my friends
when they're worried about their future,
こんな感じじゃ説得力ないから
I don't really have a leg
to stand on right now.
So, at the very least, I want
to do a proper job here.
せめてここの仕事はちゃんとやろうって…
ちょっと 父ちゃん
Hey, Pa!
やっぱり 八軒君 うちの婿に来てもらおうよ
We really should get Hachiken-kun
to marry into our family!
Why's that necessary?!
何でそうなるんだよー！
Why not? He's hard working!
働き者でいいじゃない
I won't accept him!
認めんぞ！
父さーん じいちゃーん 大変 大変
Dad!
Grandpa!
We have a problem!
What's the matter?
どしたぁ？
町営牧場の牛が脱走してきて
A whole bunch of cows from
the town ranch got loose
うちの牛と交ざっちゃった
and now they're all
mixed up with our cows!
Where'd they all come from?
どっから湧いたんですか
この近くに農家から若牛預かって放牧してる場所があるんだ
There's a nearby pasture where they let
young heifers from other farms graze.
どっか柵壊して出てきたんだべ
They must've broken through a
fence and walked off.
何頭くらいいるんでしょう
How many are there, you think?
３００はいるべなぁ
At least three hundred.
We wouldn't want our cows
若い牛に追われてうちのがケガしたら困るし
to get chased by the
heifers and get injured.
分けて収容するか
Let's separate them
out and corral them.
I have no idea which is which.
俺にはどっちがどっちだか…
You can tell by looking
at their udders.
乳房見たら分かるべや
町営牧場のは未経産牛でこれから成長する乳房
The city ranch cows have
never been milked,
so their udders still have to develop.
うちのは経産牛だから母ちゃんみたいに垂れて…
Ours have been, so theirs are
hanging like Ma's—
ええーと 町営牧場のは若いから
Okay, so the city ranch
cows are young,
which means they'll get... bigger...
これから大きく…
何見てんだ この野郎！
What the hell you looking at?!
Ow! Sorry! Sorry!
すいません！
畑荒らされる前に
Shouldn't we herd all of
them into the exercise pen
全部まとめて運動場に追い込んだ方がよくない
before they tear up the fields?
うん そうしよっか
Yeah, let's do that.
Come on, get in there.
ほれ そっち行きな
Hey, get a move on.
こら 動くんだよ おい
Hey!
This isn't working.
駄目だ こりゃ
人手が足らんわ
We don't have the manpower.
よそに応援頼みましょ
Let's go ask for help.
Mikage Ranch
landmark here
horse paddock and
cattle shed
Not that way!
そっちじゃない こっちだ こっち
This way! Over here!
What?!
何だぁ！？
スーパーカブ！？
A Super Cub?!
おーい 邪魔するな
Hey, don't interfere!
Whoa, nicely done.
お～ 見事
Who is that?
誰だ あれ
So cool!
カッコイイ～！
What?
あ…痛て…
Ow...
おい 大丈夫か
Hey, you all right?
Eh? What the hell?
うわ！？ 何だ こりゃあ！
Is cow dung this sticky?
牛のふんってこんなべちゃべちゃなのかよ
That voice...
その声は…
おう 勇吾 久しぶりだな
Hey, Yuugo!
Been a while!
兄貴…
Bro...
Hachiken's got it tough,
八軒も大変だよな
あんな兄ちゃんと比べられちゃ
being compared to a brother like his.
But that means Hachiken wouldn't
be so shabby, either, right?
でもよ 八軒だって基本性能はいいってことだろ
何でここにいるんだよ 兄貴
Why're you here, Bro?
Mom asked me to try
to get in touch with you.
おふくろに頼まれたんだよ 勇吾と連絡取れないからって
ほっといてくれよ
Leave me alone.
ちょうどバイクで北海道回っててな
I just happened to be going
around Hokkaido on my bike.
ついでに高校寄ったら寮閉まってるし
But when I went by your high
school, the dorm was closed.
御影って子の家に泊まり込んでるって聞いたぞ
I heard you were staying with
someone called Mikage.
Are you mooching?
お前 ヒモなの
バイトだよ
I work here!
今時期バイクで北海道回ってるって
You have enough time to ride around
Hokkaido on a bike at this time of year.
学生さんか何かかい？
Are you a student?
He's in college.
大学生 東京の大学に行ってるんです
He goes to a university in Tokyo.
Wow, that's quite far.
遠い所だね～
何大
Which one?
東大
Tokyo University.
Oh, I quit.
大学は辞めちった
You quit?!
辞めた！？
今はラーメン作ってる
I make ramen now.
Ramen?!
ラーメン！？
東京で食ったラーメンがうまくってさ
The ramen I had in Tokyo was so good!
It just spoke to me.
I knew this was it!
「これだ！」ってびびっときたね
What does that mean?!
どれだよ！？
Well, if I can say so myself,
いや 俺って自分で言うのも何だけど
I have a great sense of taste.
味覚はいいんだよね
When I correctly identified all the broth
ingredients to the ramen shop owner,
スープのレシピ言い当てたら
おやっさんに認められてさ
その場で弟子入りしちゃった
he accepted me as his
apprentice on the spot!
せっかく東大入ったのにもったいねえな
But you got into Tokyo University.
What a waste.
いやぁ 俺みたいなのが入れるんだから
Well, if even someone
like me can get in,
Tokyo University's not that big a deal.
東大とか大したことないっすよ
受かるための勉強法とかありましてね
There's a way to study so that
you'll pass the entrance exam.
へえ
Do you get it now, Mikage?
分かるか 御影
死ぬ気で勉強やってきて挫折した人間のライフゲージを根こそぎ持っていくこいつの言動！
How his words and actions
just totally gut you when
you put your life into studying
but still failed in the end?
Man, all this running
around's made me hungry.
走り回ったら腹減ったなぁ
そういや昼飯まだだったな
Come to think of it,
we haven't had lunch.
畑の残りは午後からだな
Let's do the rest of the
fieldwork this afternoon.
ああ
Okay.
俺 くいだけ運んどきます
I'll just carry the stakes over first!
兄ちゃん 牛追ってくれてありがとな
Well, thanks for herding the cows, buddy.
何もないけど飯食ってけや
We don't have much,
but come join us for lunch!
Oh, how about I make
ramen for you?
何なら俺が作りましょうか ラーメン
さっすが農家
It's great that farms
have big pots like these.
でかい鍋が普通にある
豚肉切らしちゃってんだわ
We're out of pork.
Oh, can you use this?
そうだ これ使えるかね 鹿肉
It's venison.
Oh!
Hachiken-kun cleaned a deer
that got hit by a car.
車ではねたやつを八軒君がさばいたのよ
Not bad.
やるなぁ あいつ
おっ そうだ おふくろに電話しなくっちゃ
Oh, right.
I should call Mom...
No Signal
…って あれ？
Uh, what?
Yeah, there's nothing to worry about.
ああ 心配することないって
学校も見てきた
I saw the school, too.
He seems to be having fun.
面白くやってるみたいだよ
He made pizza.
ピザ焼いたりとか
Pizza?
ピザ？学校で？
At school?
Yeah.
Anyway, he seems to be having fun,
まあ 楽しんでるみたいだから 当分放っといてあげてよ
so just let him be for now—
Pizza?
ピザだと？
ええ 勇吾が学校で…
Yes, Yuugo made it at school...
くだらん 代われ
Rubbish. Give me the phone.
Wait, Dear—
ちょっと お父さん…
Shingo?
慎吾か 何してる
What're you up to?
勇吾に会いに山奥に来てま～す
I'm deep in the mountains,
visiting Yuugo!
That's not what I meant.
そうではない
なぜ大学を辞めた
Why did you drop out?
To annoy you.
嫌がらせ
You told me to get into a good
college, so I did, for you.
「いい大学入れ」っつったから入ってあげたでしょ
そっちのメンツは立てたから
I let you have your day in the sun,
後は俺の好きなことをやらせてもらいますよ
so I'll do what I want
to do from now on.
揃いも揃ってろくでもない
You're both worthless sons.
勇吾は そばにいるのか
Is Yuugo there?
He's working at his part-time job.
バイト先で仕事中だよ
そのバイト先を教えろ
Tell me where.
嫌で～す さいなら～
Nope.
Bye!
Parents shouldn't butt in when their
children are working really hard.
子供が頑張ってんのに
親がしゃしゃり出てくるなんてやぼですよね
So uncivilized.
Don't you agree?
そう思いませんか
Oh, I'll get right on it!
あっ すぐ作ります
お待っとおさん
Here you go!
There was no pork,
豚肉がなかったので
so I tried to make venison char siu!
鹿肉をチャーシューにしてみました
あれ？この鹿肉って…
Huh? Is this venison from...
聞いたぞ 勇吾
I heard what you did, Yuugo.
鹿 さばいたんだって？
You cleaned a deer!
Amazing!
すげえな
Let's see how far you've come!
お手並み拝見といこうか
いただきま～す
Thanks for the food!
まっずい
This tastes horrible!
Jeez... What is this?
もう何だよ これ！？ まずっ！ びっくりだよ！
I'm shocked!
ホントびっくりだよね
Yeah, isn't it shocking?
俺って味覚のセンスはあっても
Even though I have a
great sense of taste,
I don't have a good sense of cooking.
料理のセンスはないんだよ
I went through so much
for this venison...
苦労してさばいた鹿肉を…
何か心がへし折れる
I kind of feel let down.
Oh, Great-Granny's got
quite an appetite!
あら～ ひいばあちゃんいい食べっぷり
うれしいね
That makes me happy.
うおっ でかっ
Whoa! Huge!
まだこいつらは小さい方だよ
These ones are actually still small.
ばんえい馬でしたっけ
These are for Ban'ei racing, right?
競馬ってもうかるんでしょ
Doesn't horse racing make good money?
いやぁ 昔は良かったけどね
Nah, though it used to.
Even if you put everything
into raising them,
かわいがって育てても肉用になっちゃうのが多いしな
they often become horse meat.
まっ 年寄りの道楽みたいなもんだ
You could say it's an old man's hobby.
Hey, Bro.
おい 兄貴
Don't interrupt our work.
仕事の邪魔すんなよな
してないよ 失礼な
I'm not! Don't be rude.
You've gotten the hang of this.
慣れたもんだなぁ
一応これでも馬術部員だしな
I am a member of the
equestrian club, after all.
農業高校といい部活といい意外だよなぁ
First the agricultural high school,
and now this club of yours.
I didn't expect that from you.
お前動物好きだっけ？
Do you even like animals?
俺だってこんな高校生活予想してなかったよ
I didn't expect my high school
life to be like this, either.
少し見てきたけど いい学校じゃん エゾノー
I only got a glimpse,
but Ezonoo seems like a good school.
Well, it's not a bad school.
まあ 悪い学校じゃないよ
いい豚いっぱいいたし
There were lots of good pigs, too!
あれチャーシューにしたらうまそうだなぁ
I bet they'll be super
tasty as char siu.
いやぁ うまいといえば この家の飯うまいな
Speaking of tasty,
the food here is awesome.
It's all fresh!
全部 取れたて
久しぶりにまともな飯食ったよ
I haven't had a good meal
in a long time.
普段どうやって暮らしてんだよ
How've you been getting by?
I take on part-time jobs wherever I go.
行く先々でバイトしたりな
あしたも早えんだわ
I have an early start tomorrow, too.
で お前 時給どれくらいなの？
So what's your hourly pay?
さあ 時給ってわけじゃ…
Well, it's not really
paid by the hour...
So a job like this is per diem?
こういうバイトは日当か
So, are you mooching, after all?
お前 やっぱヒモなの？
Hachiken-kun, thanks for all
of your hard work until now!
八軒君
長いことバイトお疲れさま
Oh, I'm sorry I couldn't
be of more help.
いやぁ あんまお役に立てなくてすいませんでした
That's not true!
そんなことないよ すごく助かった
You were a huge help!
お給料弾んじゃうからね
You'll be paid extra!
やった 報酬
Yay! Compensation!
Here, your compensation.
はい 報酬
ごめんね 現物支給で
Sorry that we have to
pay you in goods...
でもこの子大きく育てばいい値で売れるから
But if this one grows up nice and big,
you can sell it for a good price!
投資みたいなもんだべ
Think of it as an investment.
You can always eat it yourself.
自分で食べるって手もあるぞ
Bye!
ホントすいません
I'm so sorry.
兄貴のやつ 朝飯まで食ってったそうで
I can't believe my brother
even had breakfast here.
うまそうに食ってったなぁ
He did seem to enjoy it.
Although it's nothing special,
大したもん出せねえけど 都会の人には取れたてがうまいんだべ
city folks think freshly picked
food tastes really good.
そういや 取れたてのうまさは ピザ会のとき西川も言ってたな
Come to think of it,
Nishikawa mentioned something
about that at the pizza party.
Does milk also taste the best
when it's freshly squeezed?
牛乳も搾りたてが一番うまいんですかね？
ああ
Yup, we normally boil it first,
普段は沸かして飲んでるけど 生はうまいよ
but raw milk is great!
Oh, can I try—
それ 飲んでみても…
No.
駄目
食品衛生法で加熱殺菌していない生乳は
The Food Sanitation Act stipulates
that raw, non heat-sterilized milk
商い用にしちゃいけないことになってる
cannot be sold as a product.
そっかー
I see.
ただし 自分ちで飲む分については 特に決まりがなかったりするわけで
But there's no particular law against
drinking some in your own home.
まあ 自己責任っつーか
Well, it's your own responsibility.
例えば俺が見てないところで
For example, if you were
to take it upon yourself
八軒君が勝手にバルク開けて生乳飲んじゃって
to open the bulk tank without my
knowledge and drink raw milk,
もし腹壊しちゃっても 俺知らねえっつーか
it's not my problem, even if
you get an upset stomach.
Yup, not my problem!
知らねったら知～らね
Pro
Prostr
Prostrati
Prostration
八軒君は反応が大げさで面白いなぁ
Hachiken-kun, it's fun
to watch you overreact.
いや ホントうまいんですもん
But it's so good.
兄貴も味覚に自信あるって言ってたし
Your brother said he had faith
in his sense of taste, too.
Maybe you both have a
good sense of taste.
兄弟揃っていい舌してんでねえの
Is that so? Is it just in our genes?
何ですかね 遺伝とか
そりゃ あれだべ
Well, it's because, you know?
君らの親がちゃんとしたもの食べさせてくれてたんだべ
Your parents made sure you guys
had good food growing up.
おう バイト 早くしろ
Hey, farmhand! Hurry up!
搾乳室に牛入れるぞ
Time to herd the cows
into the milking room!
あっ はい
Oh, okay!
搾乳開始っと
Starting milking process...
すっかり手際よくなったな
You've totally gotten the hang of this.
いやぁ もう３週間以上やってますから
Well, I've been at this for
over three weeks, after all.
Time sure does fly.
早いもんだなぁ
学校戻んのは…
When do you go back to school?
あさってです
The day after tomorrow.
あっという間でした
It went by in a flash!
八軒君 よく頑張ったよなぁ
Hachiken-kun, you put
in your best effort.
まあまあだな
Not bad.
Maybe we'll pay you extra!
バイト代弾んどくか
Pay...
バイト代かぁ
何買おうかな
I wonder what I'll spend it on.
The pipe's come loose!
パイプが外れてる
All the milk's spilling out!
牛乳全部こぼれてるよー！
What?!
Man, oh man...
やっちまったー
Now we've done it.
What a waste.
もったいねえなー
いつから外れてたの これ
When'd this happen?
Oh, I...
あ…俺…
さっき パイプつなぎ忘れた…
I forgot to connect the pipe earlier...
じゃあ 最初からか
So, it was off from the start?
I guess that means we've
spilled quite a bit.
ってことはかなりの量捨てちまったなぁ
Yeah, I'd say about
five hundred liters.
５００リットルってとこか
What's done is done.
やっちまったもんはしょうがねえわ
さっさと残りの牛も搾るべ
Let's milk the rest of the herd.
アキ ここ奇麗に流しておけ
Aki, get this cleaned up.
Okay.
はーい
ぼーっとすんな
Snap out of it!
早く搾らんと残りの牛が乳房炎になる
If we don't milk the rest of 'em
soon, they'll get mastitis!
悩んでる暇なんてないんだよ
There's no time to get hung up over it!
Okay...
はい…
あのさ…
Um...
How much does milk cost?
牛乳の値段って幾らくらいするの？
So five hundred liters would be
forty thousand yen...
５００リットルだと４万円
俺のミスで４万円どぶに捨てた
My mistake sent forty thousand
yen down the drain...
いや 待て
Wait, if you deduct overhead costs like
feed costs from the purchase price,
それ以前に買い取り価格から餌代とか経費もろもろ引いたら…
how much of that even
makes it to the farmers?
農家の手元に残るのって…
おはようございます
Oh, good morning.
When did you wake up, Hachiken-kun?
八軒君 何時に起きたんだ？
I woke up a bit earlier than usual.
ちょっと早く目が覚めちゃって
Today's my last day on the job, so...
仕事できるの今日が最後だから
I'll go bring the cows in.
牛入れてきます
ちょっと 八軒君
Wait, Hachiken-kun!
アキ やらせとけ
Aki! Let him.
Hello!
こんにちは
Oh, the Komaba twins.
駒場んとこの双子じゃん
What's up?
どうした
よかった まだ帰ってなかった
Oh good, you're still here.
I'm going home tomorrow.
あした帰るけど… 何 俺に用？
Why?
You wanted to see me?
We wanted you to eat these!
食べてもらおうと思って
ありがとな 今日の夜にでも…
Thanks.
I'll have them tonight, maybe—
Oh, nice corn.
あら いいトウキビ
初物だよ さっきもいできたばっかり
It's our first harvest!
We just picked them!
Please eat them with everyone!
みんなで食べて
Oh, my!
まあ まあ それはすぐゆでなきゃねぇ
We'll have to boil them right away.
Hachiken-kun, we're taking
a break and we need a pot.
八軒君 一休みするから鍋持っといで
昨日ラーメンゆでたやつ
The one we boiled ramen in yesterday.
But I—
でも…
It's time for a mid-afternoon snack!
３時のおやつよ いいから持っといで
Just bring it!
アキはブロック
Aki, bring cinder blocks.
はーい
Okay!
There you go!
はいはいはいっと
Ow!
あっち あちちちっ
Hot, hot, hot...
So sweet!
甘っ
何だこれ 砂糖入ってんの
What is this?
Did you add sugar?
Why're you here?!
何で兄貴がいるんだよ
バイト首になっちゃって
I got fired.
首？
Fired?
ああ で腹減っちゃってさ
Yeah, then I got hungry.
Anyway, this is super sweet.
しっかし甘いな
これ特別な品種
Is it a special variety?
No, it's the normal kind
you can find anywhere.
どこにでもある普通のだよ
The sweetness of corn fades
rapidly once you pick it.
トウキビはもいだ瞬間から 甘さがぐんぐん落ちてくの
こういうの食べれるのは現場の特権
So eating it when it's like this
is a privilege of farmers.
Although farmers have it tough,
農家は苦労する分 収穫の喜びも味わえるのよ
we can also savor the joys of
the harvest that much more.
Do you like it?
おいしい
Yeah, it's super tasty!
うん 超うまい
Yeah!
That makes me happy!
やったー（うれしいなー）
二野が種まきしたの
I planted the seeds!
三空が雑草取ったの
I weeded them!
キツネよけの柵も２人で作ったよ
The two of us built the
fox fence together, too!
そんな苦労して作ったの 俺に？
After all that work,
you gave them to me?
Yeah!
この前 牛の餌やり手伝ってもらったから
You helped us feed the cows.
おっ トウキビ
Oh, corn?
ちょっと待ってろ
Hold on a sec!
You gotta have 'em this way!
やっぱこれだろ
Here, have one!
ほら 食え
Here!
ほれ
Th-Thank you!
あ…ありがとうございます
Hot, hot!
あちちっ
うまーっ！
Awesome!
ナスも焼くべ
Let's grill some eggplant.
あっ しょうゆが足りない
Oh, we don't have enough soy sauce.
味噌持ってこいや
Bring miso.
はいはい
Right on!
したっけねー
See you!
Take care!
気を付けてなー
じゃあ 俺も
I should be going, too.
ごっそさんでした また来ま～す
Thank you for letting me join in.
I'll come again.
うるさい もう来んな！
Shut up!
Don't come any more!
じゃ～な～
Later!
Hachiken-kun.
八軒君
はい
Yes?
Come here for a sec.
ちょっといらっしゃい
Okay...
はあ…
Payment
Hachiken-dono
お疲れさまでした
Thanks for your hard work.
夏休みの間 ホントに助かったわ
You were a huge help to us
during your summer vacation.
Good job.
お疲れさま
Um, I can't accept this.
あの…俺 受け取れません
何で
Why?
何でって…
昨日すごい迷惑掛けちゃって…
I caused you so much trouble yesterday.
大事な商品を大量に捨てる羽目に…
I wasted so much of your
valuable product...
That couldn't be helped.
あれはしょうがないわ
It's Gramps and Pa's
fault for not checking.
一緒にいたじいちゃんと父ちゃんが チェックしなかったのも悪いもん
だなー
Yep.
So, here!
だから はい
じゃあ せめて損失分を弁償…
Then please at least let me
compensate you for the loss—
あのね 八軒君
Listen, Hachiken-kun.
この夏休みの間
This is the amount we, your employers,
君の働きについてここに入ってる金額の価値があるって
found your work here over your
summer break to be worth.
私ら雇い主が認めたってことなのよ この給料は
でも…
But...
いいから受け取れ
Just accept it.
人間のやることだもの
We're only human.
たまには失敗することもあるっしょ
We all make mistakes sometimes.
ただし 命が関わってるときは失敗したらいかんよ
Just don't make mistakes
when lives are at stake.
ありがたく頂きます
I accept with gratitude.
苦労して 苦い思いをして手に入れた金だ
It's money he's earned through hard work.
そうそうバカなことに使おうとは思わんべ
I don't think he'll waste
it on anything frivolous.
The fool will spend his
money on worthless things.
バカはろくでもないものに金を使う
賢いやつは自分の成長のために使う
The wise will spend his
money to better himself.
男の価値は金の使い方で分かるもんさ
A man's worth can be measured
by how he spends his money.
たまには手紙を書いてみようよ
どっかにポストカードでもあったけ
懐かしい顔に見けて
ほんの数行ノスタルジーを
調子はどうですか
忙しくしていますか
無我夢中で探しまわってた
あの夢の具合はどんなだい
気分転換くらいのノリで
一緒に歌わないか
そして無我夢中で探しまわってた
あの夢の続きを語り合おうよ
明日は頑張ろうぜ
今はそこにある未来へ
駆け出して さぁ 行こう
This story is a work of fiction.
The people and groups are fictitious, but the themes relating to food and life are firmly based in reality. Visiting the places and facilities used as models can be dangerous and may result it contracting diseases from the animals. Please enjoy this story as a work of fiction.